Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, 1951-1998
  - Middle Atlantic District Council, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Middle Atlantic District Council, 1978-1979 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Middle Atlantic District Council, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Middle Atlantic District Council, 1981-1984 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Middle Atlantic District Council, 1985-1991 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Military Service Cards, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Miller, Milt (FrontPage), 1952-1953 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Minimum Wage Schedules, 1952-1953 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Minority Jobs, 1972; 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Minority Jobs, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Minority Jobs, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Minority Jobs, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Minority Jobs, 1981-1985 (Box 116a, Folder 1)
  - Minority Rights (Executive Committee), 1971 (Box 116a, Folder 2)
  - Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center, 1981 (Box 116a, Folder 3)
  - Monopolies and the Newspaper Crisis: Clippings, 1951-1972 (Box 116a, Folder 4)
  - Montes, Bill (Local Representative), 1982 (Box 116a, Folder 5)
  - Moody, William: New York Newspaper Guild v. Graphic Communications International Union (Severance Pay Case), 1989 (Box 116a, Folder 6)
  - Moonlighting, 1964 (Box 116a, Folder 7)
  - MORE's A.J. Liebling Counter-Convention, 1975 (Box 116a, Folder 8)
  - Morgenthau, Robert: Morgenthau Ticket and the Kennedy Program (Governmental Race), 1962 (Box 116a, Folder 9)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center: Joint Newspaper Guild-Mount Sinai Health Survey Questions, 1981 (Box 116a, Folder 10)
  - Mtimkulu: Phillip Mtimkulu Defense Fund (Secretary of South Africa's Union of Black Journalists), 1978 (Box 116a, Folder 11)
  - Municipal Photographers Welfare Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 116a, Folder 12)
  - Murphy, Joseph P. (President), 1955-1956 (Box 116a, Folder 13)
  - Murphy, Thomas J. (Executive Vice-President): Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 116a, Folder 14)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 116a, Folder 15)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 116a, Folder 16)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 116a, Folder 17)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 116a, Folder 18)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (I), 1968 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (II), 1968 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (III), 1968 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (IV), 1968 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (I), 1969 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (II), 1969 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (III), 1969 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (IV), 1969 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (I), 1971 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Correspondence (II), 1971 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: General, 1963-1964 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: General, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Local "Pending", 1969-1970 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Murphy, Thomas J.: Retirement, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Nassau-Suffolk CIO, 1954 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Nassau-Suffolk CIO, 1955-1956 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Commission of Labor-Management Organization, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - National Manpower Institute, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - National Conference On Unit Clarification Petitions, 1979 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1950s (Box 118a, Folder 1)
  - NLRB, 1960s (Box 118a, Folder 2)
  - NLRB, 1970s (Box 118a, Folder 3)
  - NLRB, 1980s (Box 118a, Folder 4)
  - NLRB: Erie-Niagara Publishing v. Buffalo Newspaper Guild (Local 26), 1975 (Box 118a, Folder 5)
  - NLRB: Hugh Riley and Mark Sonnenblick v. Newspaper Guild of New York (GTE North), 1989-1990 (Box 118a, Folder 6)
  - NLRB: News Syndicate Company v. Newspaper Guild of New York (I), 1966 (Box 118a, Folder 7)
  - NLRB: News Syndicate Company v. Newspaper Guild of New York (II), 1966 (Box 118a, Folder 8)
  - NLRB: Nowy Swiat Publishing Corporation (Polish Language Newspaper), 1961 (Box 118a, Folder 9)
  - NLRB: Register Publishing Company v. Newspaper Guild of New York (Sexual Bias), 1976 (Box 118a, Folder 10)
  - NLRB: Westchester Rockland Group, 1972 (Box 118a, Folder 11)
  - National Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and Southern Africa (President Ronald Reagan), 1987 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - National Safety Council, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - National Student Coalition Against Racism, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Negotiation Committee, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Industrial Union Council (AFL-CIO), 1980s (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - New Jersey Unemployment Insurance Appeals, 1963 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey Units of Newspaper Guild of New York Meeting, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - New Officers' Seminar, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), 1951-1959 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), 1960-1970 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), 1971-1980 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), 1981-1986 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO), 1987-1988 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO): Central Labor Rehabilitation Council Job Development, 1950s (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (AFL-CIO): Labor Day Parade, 1960-1990 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - New York City Civil Liberties Union: Norwick v. Rockefeller, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - New York City CIO Council Committee: Israel Histadrut Campaign in America, 1951 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - New York City Department of Labor, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - New York Consumer Assembly, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - New York Institute of Technology: Newspaper Guild of New York Program, 1981-1983 (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - New York Legislative Service: Labor Internship, 1964 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - New York Local Defense Fund, 1959; 1963 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - New York Press Club, 1987-1988 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - New York State Advisory Manpower Panel, 1964-1965 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - New York State Advisory Manpower Panel, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - New York State Advisory Manpower Panel, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - New York State Advisory Manpower Panel, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - New York State Allied Printing and Trades Convention, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - New York State Allied Printing and Trades Convention, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1968-1979 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1981; 1989 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1958-1959 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1963-1967 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Convention, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - New York State Board of Mediation, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - New York State CIO, 1951 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - New York State CIO, 1952 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - New York State CIO, 1953 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - New York State CIO, 1954 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - New York State CIO, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - New York State CIO, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - New York State CIO, 1957 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - New York State CIO, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - New York State CIO, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - New York State CIO Convention, 1951 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - New York State CIO Convention, 1953 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - New York State CIO Convention, 1954 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - New York State CIO Convention, 1955-1957 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1956-1958 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - New York State Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH), 1980-1988 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - New York State Department of Labor, 1981 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights Requests for Guild Shop Statistics, 1984-1985 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - New York State Human Rights Board, 1984-1985 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - New York Telephone Company Communication Workers of America Strike, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - New York Urban Coalition, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Newhouse Contracts, 1978-1981 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Newsmen: Freedom of Operation, 1970 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Enterprise Association Contract, 1974-1976 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1975 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1976 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1978 (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1979 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1984 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1992 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Guild Convention, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Guild: Employees (Citizens of Industrial Employees), 1952 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Guild: History (Literature), 1953-1960s (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union (NMDU), 1950-1988 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - NMDU: Bulletin, 1981-1982 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - NMDU: Strike, 1958-1959 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - NMDU: Strike (Contributions to Emergency Fund), 1958-1959 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Newsletter, 1985-1988 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Trades Council, 1964-1965 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Newsprint Price Increase, 1952-1957 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - North Jersey Newspaper Guild, 1976-1977 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Oath of Office, 1976; 1979 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Occupational Health and Safety Research Institute, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - O'Farrell, Mary, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Office Employees International Union (OEIU), 1961-1963 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - OEIU, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - OEIU, 1965-1968 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 1969-1975 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - OPEIU, 1976-1985 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Office Procedures, 1965; 1968 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Office Supplies: Inventory, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Open Shop (Magazines Committee), 1979-1980 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training, 1956 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Orcutt, James H.: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Organizing, 1951-1956 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Organizing, 1958-1963 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - Organizing, 1964-1967 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Organizing, 1968-1970 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - Organizing, 1971-1974 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - Organizing, 1975-1978 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Organizing, 1979-1988 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Organizing Committee, 1950s (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Organizing Committee, 1964;1976-1982 (Box 124, Folder 3a)
  - Ostrin, Hy (Attorney): Retirement Party, 1976 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1952-1953 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1954-1955 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1956-1957 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1958-1959 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1960 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1964 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1965 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1966 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1972 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1975-1976 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1977-1978 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Out of Town Locals, 1982 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Page One Advertising, 1956 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Page One Advertising, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Page One Advertising, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Page One Advertising, 1962 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Page One Advertising (I), 1964 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Page One Advertising (II), 1964 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Page One Advertising (III), 1964 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Page One Advertising (IV), 1964 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Page One Advertising, 1965 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Page One Advertising, 1966 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Page One Advertising, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Page One Advertising, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Page One Advertising, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Page One Advertising, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Page One Advertising, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Page One Advertising, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Page One Advertising, 1975 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Page One Advertising, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Page One Awards, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Page One Awards, 1965 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Page One Awards, 1966 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Page One Awards, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Page One Awards, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Page One Awards, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Page One Awards, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Page One Awards, 1972 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Page One Awards, 1973-1974 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Page One Awards, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Page One Awards, 1976-1977 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Page One Awards, 1979 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Page One Awards, 1980 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Page One Awards, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Page One Awards, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Page One Awards, 1986 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Page One Ball, 1951 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Page One Ball, 1952-1953 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Page One Ball, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Page One Ball, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Page One Ball, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Page One Ball, 1961-1962 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Page One Ball, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Page One Ball, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Page One Ball, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Page One Ball: Buffalo Guild, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Page One Ball: Clippings, 1955 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Page One Ball: Clippings, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Page One Ball: Clippings, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - Page One Ball: Miss Page One Contest (Photos), 1965 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - Page One Ball: Roz Starr Daily Communiqué, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - Page One: General, 1950s (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Page One: General, 1960s (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Page One: General, 1970s (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Page One: Theatre, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Page One: Yearbook, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Page One: Yearbook, 1969 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Page One: Yearbook, 1972-1974 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Pay Board, 1971-1974 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Pay Board: Clippings, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Pay Board Rollback: Pressmen's and Stereotyper's Claim, 1975 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Payroll Information, 1965-1966 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Peace Corps, 1961 (Box 128, Folder 11a)
  - Pennacchio, Thomas (Secretary-Treasurer): Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Pennacchio, Thomas: General, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Pension, 1951 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Pension, 1952 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Pension, 1953 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Pension, 1954 (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Pension, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - Pension, 1956 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Pension, 1957 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - Pension (I), 1958 (Box 128, Folder 21)
  - Pension (II), 1958 (Box 128, Folder 22)
  - Pension, 1959 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Pension, 1960 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Pension, 1962 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Pension, 1963 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Pension, 1964 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Pension, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Pension, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Pension, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Pension, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Pension, 1970 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Pension, 1971 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Pension, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Pension, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Pension, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Pension, 1975 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Pension, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Pension, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Pension, 1978 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Pension, 1979 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Pension, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Pension, 1982 (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Pension, 1983 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Pension, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Pension, 1985 (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Pension, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Pension, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Pension, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Pension, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Pension: San Francisco Retirement Income Plan, 1956-1957 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Pension: Second Year Increase, 1957 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Per Capita Payments, 1975-1980 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Perlik, Charles A., Jr. (President): Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Perlik: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Perlik: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Perlik: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Pflaster, Bea Eastman (President's Executive Secretary): Retirement, 1986-1987 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Photoengravers' Strike, 1953 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Photoengravers' Strike: Clippings, 1953 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Photoengravers Union, 1964-1983 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Photography: Fashion Photography Clippings (Stan Papish, Bill Sauro, Finklestein, Whitestone, James Kavallines, et al.), 1960s (Box 130a, Folder 1)
  - Pilat, Oliver (President): Correspondence, 1965 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Newspaper Guild: Rehiring Clause Query, 1957 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Placement Service: Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Police Department, City of New York (Press Credentials), 1958; 1961 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Police Department, City of New York (Protection for Members of the Press), 1968-1969 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Policy Memos (Office Behavior), 1982 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Polish Resolutions (Solidarnosc), 1982 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Political Action Committee, 1951 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Political Action Committee, 1952 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Political Action Committee, 1953 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Political Action Committee, 1954 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Political Action Committee, 1955 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Political Action Committee, 1956 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Political Action Committee, 1957-1958, undated (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Poor People's Campaign, 1968 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Portland, Oregon Strike, 1960-1961 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Portland, Oregon Strike: Clippings, 1960-1961 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Portland, Oregon Strike: Christmas Fund, 1960 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Postal Rate Increases, 1962; 1972; 1981 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Potoker, M. Michael (Secretary-Treasurer): Correspondence, 1951 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1952 (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1953 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1955 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1957 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1958 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1959 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Pregnancy Disability Act, 1976-1980 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Press: Civilian Defense (Loyalty Oaths), 1951-1952 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Press: Employment requirements for Photography, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Pressmen's' Negotiations, 1978 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Price Increases, 1972 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Printing and Kindred Trades Federation, 1965-1968 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Privacy: Celebrity Rights (Senator Emanuel Gold), 1988 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Productivity and Job Security: The Value of an Attrition Clause (Robert Zagar), 1976 (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers' Strike, 1981-1982 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Profit Sharing Plan with the New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union, 1983 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Providence Newspaper Guild (Providence Journal Company Arbitrations), 1974 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - Publication: City Wide, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 19)
  - Publication and Education Committee, 1953 (Box 132, Folder 20)
  - Publishers: Members of the Publishers' Payroll under Guild Jurisdiction, 1950s (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Publishers Association of New York City (Contract Proposals), 1981 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rican Labor Advisory Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 132, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico: El Mundo Strike, 1972 (Box 132, Folder 24)
  - Ramsey, Richard J. (Washington-Baltimore Newspaper Guild): Correspondence, 1981 (Box 132, Folder 25)
  - Rank and File (Simon W. Gerson; Smith Act), 1951-1952 (Box 132, Folder 26)
  - Reagan Administration's Labor Law Record, 1981-1984 (Box 132, Folder 27)
  - Real Estate, 1955; 1981 (Box 132, Folder 28)
  - Recruitment, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Religious Leaders Committee, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Remittances, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press, 1975; 1981 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Representative Assembly, 1951 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Representative Assembly, 1952 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Representative Assembly, 1953 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Representative Assembly, 1954 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Representative Assembly, 1955 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Representative Assembly, 1956 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Representative Assembly, 1957 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Representative Assembly, 1958 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Representative Assembly, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Representative Assembly, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Representative Assembly, 1961 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Representative Assembly, 1962 (Box 133, Folder 16)